<resources>
    <string name="app_name">all hands</string>

    <string name="UNICEF">UNICEF, or the United Nations Children\'s Fund, is a United Nations agency responsible for providing humanitarian and developmental aid to children worldwide. UNICEF was established in 1946 to help children in the aftermath of World War II, and since then, it has been working to improve the lives of children in need around the world. The organization works to provide health care, nutrition, education, and protection to children in over 190 countries and territories, with a particular focus on those who are most vulnerable and marginalized. UNICEF is funded entirely by voluntary contributions from individuals, businesses, foundations, and governments, and it works in close partnership with other organizations, including governments, NGOs, and other UN agencies, to achieve its goals\nWebsite: https://www.unicefusa.org/?form=donate</string>
    <string name="CARE_International">CARE International is a global humanitarian organization that works to fight poverty and social injustice in over 100 countries around the world. The organization focuses on empowering women and girls, improving access to healthcare and education, and responding to emergencies and disasters. CARE International works in partnership with communities, governments, and other organizations to help create lasting change and improve the lives of people in need.</string>
    <string name="link"><a href="https://www.hopelink.org/take-action/donate-goods-services">link</a></string>
    <string name="Hopelink">Hopelink is a non-profit organization based in Washington state, USA, that provides a range of services to people in need, including food assistance, emergency shelter, transportation, energy assistance, and job training. The organization\'s mission is to promote self-sufficiency for individuals and families in crisis by providing assistance and support to help them achieve stability and independence. Hopelink operates multiple centers throughout King and Snohomish counties and serves thousands of people each year. The organization relies on community support and donations to fund its programs and services.\nWebsite: https://www.hopelink.org/take-action/donate-goods-services
</string>
</resources>